ABDUL SAMEER Java Developer

L +91 96859 81869

abdulsameer9685gmail.com

New Ashok Nagar, Delhi

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology Patel College of Science & Technology, Bhopal

2018-2022

Courses 7.9 CGPA

_Mechanical Engineering

XII – Higher Secondary Navjyoti Academy School,Umaria

2017-2018

_Maths, science 74.88%

X – High School Mahakal Higher Secondary Maihar,Satna

2014-2015 56.83%

LANGUAGE

English

Limited Working Proficiency

Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Travelling

Playing Badminton

DECLARATION:-

I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.

ABOUT

To become a successful professional in the field of Information Technology and to work in an innovative and competitive world.

PROFILE SUMMARY

One year of experience in JAVA in developing projects in support of application software for the Manufacturing Process.

Currently working in K 30 IT BUSINESS SOLUTION PVT.LTD IN GR NOIDA as Java Developer.

I have experience with Java as Core Java, Spring MVC, Spring Boot, Hibernate.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Language / Frame Work Core Java, Spring Boot, Spring, Maven

Database MySQL
Web Technology JSP, Servlet
Server Tomcat
Operating System Windows
Software Versioning Tool Git (Bacis)

Employment History:

K 30 IT BUSINESS SOLUTION

1.Project Name: Cash Management May,2022-november,2022

Cash Management is designed to account for the transactions of cash expenditure. This Product describes the flow of money from accounts to the branches. And followed by the expenditure in the branch, the Transaction or Data Entry Process allows entering financial details into the system and then using this information for enquiries, reporting, analysis and verification when entering further details.

Environment- Spring-Boot, Restful, Eclipse, MySql, Apache Tomcat.

2.Project Name: Induction Feedback Form January, 2023-Present

This project is based on HR products. When an organization hire a new employee, it must provide training to the selected employee. For this purpose, the organization also hires a trainer. To know about the trainer's performance organization takes feedback from the trainer through this product.

Environment- Spring-Boot, JSP,Web-Service,MySql, Apache Tomcat.

ACHIEVEMENTS:

Winner in State level competition of Badminton.

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Name Abdul Sameer
Date of Birth 04-11-1999
Father's name Abdul Aziz
Mother's name Sex Safina begam
Male

Marital Status Unmarried